you
You want to go to college. You want to play
pretend. This silly little game of yours, I know
just how it ends. You think you're smart, my
Aubrey. You think you'll get away. But I know how
to break you. I know the words to say.
So choose the stars, my little one, choose the
great unknown A world of math you'll never pass
out there all alone It's far too hard, it's far
too cold a trap I've set for you This silly
college experiment will be your Waterloo
You'll fail your first assignment You'll panic
at the tests You'll realize you're not like them
You're not as good as them You'll see you're just
a burden Incapable and weak You'll call me
crying, begging You won't last a single week
So choose the stars, my little one. Choose the
great unknown. A world of math you'll never pass
out there all alone. It's far too hard. It's far
too cold. A trap I set for you. This silly college
experiment will be your Waterloo.
Waterloo.
It's all part of the plan.
You'll come back home. You'll come back to me.
They always come back to me.
So choose the stars, my little one Choose the
great unknown A world of math you'll never pass
out there all alone It's far too hard, it's far
too cold A trap I set for you This silly college
experiment will be your Waterloo
You'll come home
You'll fail